Guide to the Franklin Toker Papers, 1964-2017 UA.90.F108
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1973-2010; VIII.
  - Professional Correspondence, 1973-2016; 2.
    The Professional Correspondence subseries is a collection of professional letters both to and from Dr. Toker over the course of his career. Those corresponding with Toker include professors at the University of Pittsburgh and Carnegie Mellon, as well as other collegues from abroad. This subseries also includes reports, course information, news clippings, calendars, and curriculum vitae. Also present is information pertaining to the publishing of several of Dr. Toker's books, including Pittsburgh: An Urban Portrait and Fallingwater Rising.
    - Academic Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Art and Execution of the Israel Room, 1975-1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "A Question of Grit: Five Days on the Pittsburgh to Washington Bike Trail", May 2008 (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
    - Calendars, 2000-2002 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie Mellon Correspondence, 1973-1981 (Box 52, Folder 5-7)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2013-2016 (Box 52, Folder 12-14)
    - Fallingwater Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Fallingwater Rising Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence on the Israel Room, 1975-1981 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
    - Grants, 1979-1996 (Box 53, Folder 5-7)
    - Israel Heritage Room, 1976-1982 (Box 53, Folder 8-9)
    - Israel Room Letters, 1981-1983 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Job Inquiry Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh: An Urban Portrait Correspondence, 1985-1995 (Box 53, Folder 12-13)
    - Pitt Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Pitt Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 54, Folder 2-3)
    - Pitt Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 4-5)
    - Pontifical Institute of Medieval Studies, 1992-2009 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Professional Calendars, 1996-1999 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Professional Correspondence: Organizing Ideas, 1974-1996 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1979-1987 (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
    - Professional Grants and Finance Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 54, Folder 13-14)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 55, Folder 6-9)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 56, Folder 3-4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1994-2003 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Professional Correspondence, Reparata Workshop, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Professional Correspondence, HAA Department and Mini-notes, 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 11-13)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
    - Professional Correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 57, Folder 5-9)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 11-14)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 58, Folder 3-4)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 5-9)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 58, Folder 10-13)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2007-2010 (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2009-2010 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - Professional Correspondence, 2010-2017 (Box 59, Folder 5-6)
    - Sansedoni Correspondence, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Teaching Correspondence, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Toker Articles, 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1979-1995; 3.
    The Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence subseries consists of letters both to and from Dr. Toker regarding the Society of Architectural Historians, a group to which Toker was a member and former president. Also included as attachments are meeting minutes, notes, and information on SAH conferences.
    - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Society of Architectural Historians, 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Reports and Notes, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Reports and Notes, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Reports and Notes, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 5-8)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Reports and Notes, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Society of Architectural Historians Reports and Notes, 1994-1995 (Box 60, Folder 12)